Your ID card was deactivated upon your termination.
لقد تم إلغاء بطاقة الهوية الخاصة بك عند إنهاء خدمتك.
Ma'am, that's enough.
سيدتي، هذا يكفي.
- Ma'am, that's enough. - Leave me alone!
- سيدتي، هذا يكفي. - اتركيني وحدي!
Do you have any idea who I am?
هل لديك أي فكرة من أنا؟
What's going on here?
ماذا يحدث هنا؟
She's an outsider.
إنها غريبة.
Are you going to let her in?
هل ستسمح لها بالدخول؟
- Let's go, ma'am. - Let go of me!
- هيا بنا يا سيدتي. - دعيني أذهب!
Let me go! Get your hands off me!
دعني أذهب! ابعد يديك عني!
Let go!
اتركه!
I'm Min Kyung Chae of Mingang Distribution!
أنا مين كيونغ تشاي من Migang Distribution!
Let me go!
دعني أذهب!
Let go!
اتركه!
Unbelievable.
لا يصدق.
(Episode 84)
(الحلقة 84)
Hey, Yeon Ah.
مهلا، يون آه.
You know what tomorrow is, right?
هل تعلم ما هو الغد، أليس كذلك؟
Of course, I do.
بالطبع أفعل.
We have to go celebrate with Mi So.
علينا أن نذهب للاحتفال مع مي سو.
Of course.
بالطبع.
(Mingang Distribution)
(توزيع)
Did you really have to go that far?
هل كان عليك حقا أن تذهب إلى هذا الحد؟
You'll get what's coming to you for this.
سوف تحصل على ما يستحقه هذا.
What did you just say?
ماذا قلت للتو؟
Did you have to drive out the poor CEO to make yourself happy?
هل كان عليك طرد الرئيس التنفيذي المسكين لكي تشعر بالسعادة؟
Is that what you're here to argue about?
هل هذا ما أنت هنا للنقاش بشأنه؟
Listen, Baek Sul Hee.
استمع، بايك سول هي.
I know this is revenge for our daughter, but this is going too far.
أعلم أن هذا انتقام لابنتنا، لكن هذا الأمر وصل إلى حد بعيد.
Mi So wasn't just your daughter. She was my daughter, too.
مي سو لم تكن ابنتكِ فحسب، بل كانت ابنتي أيضًا.
Your daughter?
ابنتك؟
That's right. My daughter. My own flesh and blood.
هذا صحيح. ابنتي. من لحمي ودمي.
You wrecked someone else's company to steal the CEO position.
لقد دمرت شركة شخص آخر لسرقة منصب الرئيس التنفيذي.
Do you think she's looking down happy about any of this?
هل تعتقد أنها تبدو سعيدة بشأن أي من هذا؟
Don't you dare say her name with that filthy mouth.
لا تجرؤ على قول اسمها بهذا الفم القذر.
That's why...
لهذا السبب...
you've done enough.
لقد فعلت ما يكفي.
Stop this. Right now.
اوقف هذا الان.
No. I'm just getting started.
لا، أنا فقط بدأت.
Doing this won't bring her back.
إن القيام بهذا لن يعيدها.
That's why I have to do this...
لهذا السبب يجب علي أن أفعل هذا...
because she's not coming back!
لأنها لن تعود!
Since we're on the subject, do you even know what tomorrow is?
بما أننا نتحدث عن هذا الموضوع، هل تعلم ما هو الغد؟
It's Mi So's 20th birthday.
إنه عيد ميلاد مي سو العشرين.
She would have been so beautiful at the best time of her life.
لقد كانت ستكون جميلة جدًا في أفضل أوقات حياتها.
Do you know what I'm going through today?
هل تعلم ما أمر به اليوم؟
How dare you lecture me about our daughter!
كيف تجرؤ على محاضرتي بشأن ابنتنا!
After all this time, now you care?
بعد كل هذا الوقت، هل تهتم الآن؟
She was your daughter, too?
هل كانت ابنتك أيضًا؟
If you considered Mi So your daughter, you wouldn't be defending Min Kyung Chae.
إذا كنت تعتبر مي سو ابنتك، فلن تدافع عن مين كيونغ تشاي.
How can a father...
كيف يمكن للأب...
side with his own child's enemy?
إلى جانب عدو ابنه؟
You're spineless, but this is too much.
أنت ضعيف الشخصية، ولكن هذا كثير جدًا.
Who do you think did that to your daughter?
من تعتقد أنه فعل ذلك لابنتك؟
So get out of my sight.
لذلك اخرج من أمام ناظري.
You were never a father to her.
لم تكن أبا لها أبدا.
Becoming CEO has really gone to her head.
إن تولي منصب الرئيس التنفيذي أصبح أمرا غريبا بالنسبة لها.
Then again,
ثم مرة أخرى،
she's the one in charge of Mingang Distribution now.
وهي المسؤولة عن شركة Mingang Distribution الآن.
(Director Min Soo Jung)
(المخرج مين سو جونغ)
Hey!
يا!
Soo Jung!
سو جونغ!
You won't believe what I just saw.
لن تصدق ما رأيته للتو.
What now?
ماذا الآن؟
Kyung Chae was just dragged out of the building.
لقد تم سحب كيونغ تشاي للتو خارج المبنى.
Dragged out?
سحبت للخارج؟
That woman takes the CEO position, and her first act is firing Kyung Chae.
تتولى هذه المرأة منصب الرئيس التنفيذي، وأول عمل تقوم به هو طرد كيونج تشاي.
It's a bloodbath.
إنه حمام دم.
She's crossed the line.
لقد تجاوزت الخط.
Regardless of the reason, this is too much.
بغض النظر عن السبب، هذا كثير جدًا.
That's what I'm saying!
هذا ما أقوله!
Come on. No matter how much of a pain Kyung Chae is, this is just wrong.
هيا، مهما كان الألم الذي يُسببه كيونغ تشاي، فهذا خطأ.
If we let this go, we could be next.
إذا تركنا هذا الأمر، فقد نكون التاليين.
What's to stop her from coming after us?
ما الذي يمنعها من المجيء إلينا؟
She's basically declaring war by taking out her rival...
إنها تعلن الحرب بشكل أساسي من خلال القضاء على منافسها ...
after becoming CEO, right?
بعد أن أصبح الرئيس التنفيذي، أليس كذلك؟
She thinks she's untouchable now.
إنها تعتقد أنها غير قابلة للمس الآن.
I swear, that woman...
أقسم أن تلك المرأة...
Hey, Min Soo Jung! You're coming with me! Darn it.
يا مين سو جونغ! ستأتي معي! اللعنة.
(Mingang Distribution)
(توزيع)
What's all this commotion?
ما كل هذه الضجة؟
Is it true you fired my sister?
هل صحيح أنك طردت أختي؟
I heard she was just dragged out of the building.
سمعت أنها تم سحبها للتو خارج المبنى.
They dragged her out like a dog.
لقد سحبوها للخارج مثل الكلب.
That's rich.
هذا غني.
When were you ever concerned for your half-sister?
متى شعرت بالقلق على أختك غير الشقيقة؟
Excuse me?
اعذرني؟
Weren't you two worse than enemies?
ألم تكونا أسوأ من الأعداء؟
Weren't you the one who begged me to remove Min Kyung Chae as the CEO?
ألم تكن أنت الشخص الذي توسل إلي لإزالة مين كيونغ تشاي من منصب الرئيس التنفيذي؟
You did that?
هل فعلت ذلك؟
But that didn't mean I wanted you to take her place!
ولكن هذا لا يعني أنني أريدك أن تأخذ مكانها!
Have you already forgotten about your birth mother?
هل نسيت والدتك الحقيقية بالفعل؟
That's a separate issue.
وهذه قضية منفصلة.
Are you really going to fire my sister just like this?
هل حقا سوف تطرد أختي هكذا؟
She had it coming. The chairman is aware.
لقد كان يستحق ذلك. الرئيس على علم بذلك.
Can you do whatever you want as long as the chairman knows?
هل يمكنك أن تفعل ما تريد طالما أن الرئيس يعرف ذلك؟
So, does this mean Jung Lucia is calling the shots at Mingang now?
إذن، هل يعني هذا أن جونغ لوسيا هي من تتخذ القرارات في مينغانغ الآن؟
The shot caller of Mingang...
مُطلق النار على مينغانغ...
I like the sound of that.
أعجبني هذا الصوت.
So you'd better grovel.
لذلك من الأفضل أن تتواضع.
If you don't want to end up fired like your sister.
إذا كنت لا تريد أن ينتهي بك الأمر مطرودًا مثل أختك.
What are you doing home at this hour?
ماذا تفعل في المنزل في هذه الساعة؟
What's wrong, Ms. Kyung Chae?
ما الأمر يا آنسة كيونغ تشاي؟
What is it?
ما هذا؟
Don't tell me that woman kicked you out of the company.
لا تخبرني أن هذه المرأة طردتك من الشركة.
Right now, our team has an opening due to Min Kyung Chae's dismissal,
في الوقت الحالي، يوجد لدى فريقنا افتتاح بسبب طرد مين كيونج تشاي،
and that spot will be filled by a transfer from another department,
وسيتم ملء هذا المكان بنقل من قسم آخر،
or until we get a new hire.
أو حتى نحصل على موظف جديد.
Otherwise, we'll have to manage with the current team.
وإلا فسوف نضطر إلى التعامل مع الفريق الحالي.
It's going to be one or the other.
سيكون أحدهما أو الآخر.
So, what do you think?
إذن، ما رأيك؟
Let's just stick with our current team.
دعونا نلتزم بفريقنا الحالي.
A new person would just make things awkward,
الشخص الجديد سيجعل الأمور محرجة،
and to be honest, those few days were tough enough.
وبصراحة، كانت تلك الأيام القليلة صعبة بما فيه الكفاية.
I agree. We're all so in sync,
أنا أتفق. نحن جميعًا متناغمون جدًا،
and bringing in the wrong person could mess up our teamwork.
وقد يؤدي تعيين الشخص الخطأ إلى إفساد عملنا الجماعي.
That's true.
هذا صحيح.
We've been the core members since the online team formed.
لقد كنا الأعضاء الأساسيين منذ تشكيل الفريق عبر الإنترنت.
Anyone new would just feel like an outsider.
أي شخص جديد سوف يشعر وكأنه غريب.
Okay. I understand what you're all saying.
حسنًا، أفهم ما تقولونه جميعًا.
And it's true, when it comes to teamwork, no other team can touch us.
وهذا صحيح، عندما يتعلق الأمر بالعمل الجماعي، لا يمكن لأي فريق آخر أن ينافسنا.
Look at them, subtly bad-mouthing her.
انظر إليهم، يتحدثون عنها بسوء بطريقة خفية.
No matter what a wreck Kyung Chae is in right now,
بغض النظر عن مدى الحطام الذي تعيشه كيونغ تشاي الآن،
how can they be so cheerful the second she's gone?
كيف يمكنهم أن يكونوا سعداء للغاية بعد رحيلها؟
Vice Director Min.
نائب المدير العام
Do you have something to say?
هل لديك شيئا لتقوله؟
No. I have nothing to say at all.
لا، ليس لدي ما أقوله على الإطلاق.
It looks like you have something on your mind.
يبدو أن هناك شيئًا في ذهنك.
I said I don't.
قلت أنني لا أفعل.
How does it feel...
كيف تشعر...
after kicking Min Kyung Chae out of Mingang?
بعد طرد مين كيونغ تشاي من مينغانغ؟
I should feel great, but it hasn't really sunk in yet.
يجب أن أشعر بشعور رائع، لكنني لم أستوعب الأمر بعد.
Mingang was her life, her entire goal.
كان مينغانغ هو حياتها وهدفها بالكامل.
Now that she's been completely tossed aside,
الآن بعد أن تم التخلص منها تمامًا،
she's going to fall apart mentally.
إنها سوف تنهار عقليا.
I'm sure she will.
أنا متأكد من أنها ستفعل ذلك.
The CEO role was never just a title to her.
لم يكن دور الرئيس التنفيذي مجرد لقب بالنسبة لها.
Now, no matter what anyone says,
الآن، بغض النظر عما يقوله أي شخص،
you're the second-in-command at Mingang, Lucia.
أنت الرجل الثاني في القيادة في مينغانغ، لوسيا.
She won't have any power on the Board of Directors anymore, either.
ولن يكون لها أي سلطة على مجلس الإدارة بعد الآن أيضًا.
So, does the real battle for the shares start now?
فهل تبدأ المعركة الحقيقية على الأسهم الآن؟
It has to.
لا بد من ذلك.
Depending on who holds the most shares of Mingang Distribution,
اعتمادًا على من يمتلك أكبر عدد من أسهم Mingang Distribution،
the de facto owner of Mingang will be decided.
سيتم تحديد المالك الفعلي لشركة مينجانج .
The owner of Mingang...
مالك مينغانغ...
It'll be impossible to get any more shares from Chairman Min Doo Sik.
وسيكون من المستحيل الحصول على المزيد من الأسهم من رئيس مجلس الإدارة مين دو سيك.
So now, the key is...
والآن المفتاح هو...
to sway the Board's shares that were with Min Kyung Chae...
للتأثير على أسهم مجلس الإدارة التي كانت مع مين كيونج تشاي...
and bring them over to our side.
وإحضارهم إلى جانبنا.
What are you thinking so deeply about?
ما الذي تفكر فيه بعمق؟
Lucia.
لوسيا.
What about her?
ماذا عنها؟
Something about her makes me uneasy.
هناك شيء فيها يجعلني أشعر بالقلق.
I know there's nothing more unpredictable than a person's heart,
أعلم أنه لا يوجد شيء أكثر لا يمكن التنبؤ به من قلب الإنسان،
but still, this just doesn't feel right.
لكن رغم ذلك، لا يبدو هذا الأمر صحيحًا.
Has she had a change of heart or something?
هل تغيرت قلوبها أو شيء من هذا القبيل؟
I think Lucia is starting to see that girl, Se Ri, as her own daughter.
أعتقد أن لوسيا بدأت ترى تلك الفتاة، سي ري، على أنها ابنتها.
No way.
مستحيل.
She was the reason Lucia lost her child. How can that be?
كانت سببًا في فقدان لوسيا طفلها. كيف يُعقل ذلك؟
I don't think Lucia herself realizes it, but that's how I see it.
لا أعتقد أن لوسيا تدرك ذلك بنفسها، لكن هكذا أرى الأمر.
That explains why she'd jump in there to save the kid.
وهذا يفسر سبب قفزها إلى هناك لإنقاذ الطفل.
Did she grow fond of her from living in the same house?
هل أصبحت تحبها من خلال العيش معها في نفس المنزل؟
Does that even make sense?
هل هذا منطقي حقا؟
To think she married that man for revenge, only to grow fond of his own daughter.
أن تفكر في أنها تزوجت ذلك الرجل من أجل الانتقام، فقط لكي تحب ابنته.
Besides, who started this whole cursed relationship in the first place?
وبالإضافة إلى ذلك، من الذي بدأ هذه العلاقة الملعونة بأكملها في المقام الأول؟
What's up with Kyung Chae? She's been acting weird.
ما الأمر مع كيونغ تشاي؟ تتصرف بغرابة.
- She's acting like she's lost her mind. - This isn't happening!
- إنها تتصرف وكأنها فقدت عقلها. - هذا لن يحدث!
She's not in her right mind right now.
إنها ليست في حالتها الصحيحة الآن.
And how could she be?
وكيف يمكن أن تكون كذلك؟
That woman... I mean, Madam Jung...
تلك المرأة... أعني، السيدة جونغ...
I heard she had Ms. Kyung Chae fired from the company.
سمعت أنها قامت بطرد السيدة كيونغ تشاي من الشركة.
Do you still think she's so great?
هل لا تزال تعتقد أنها عظيمة جدًا؟
She must've had her reasons. She wouldn't do that for nothing.
لا بد أن لديها أسبابها. لن تفعل ذلك عبثًا.
It's going to be tense around the house,
سيكون الوضع متوترا في جميع أنحاء المنزل،
so you should get out for a little while. Go see a friend or something.
لذا عليك الخروج قليلًا. اذهب لزيارة صديق أو شيء من هذا القبيل.
Min Se Ri?
مين سي ري؟
- Who are you? - I'm your stepmom's best friend.
- من أنت؟ - أنا أفضل صديقة لزوجة أبيك.
Can we talk for a minute? I have something to tell you.
هل يمكننا التحدث لدقيقة؟ أريد أن أخبرك بشيء.
Why did you suddenly want to meet, Grandma?
لماذا فجأة أردت أن تلتقي بجدتي؟
Come to think of it, you always call me "Grandma."
إذا فكرت في الأمر، فأنت دائمًا تناديني بـ "الجدة".
I may be old enough to be one,
ربما أكون كبيرًا بما يكفي لأكون واحدًا منهم،
but I certainly don't look the part.
ولكنني بالتأكيد لا أبدو كذلك.
Whatever. You look like a grandma to me.
مهما يكن. أنتِ تبدو لي كالجدة.
Who on earth does she take after?
من على الأرض تشبه؟
She's nothing like Min Kyung Chae,
إنها لا تشبه مين كيونغ تشاي على الإطلاق،
so she's definitely not Ho Se's kid.
لذا فهي بالتأكيد ليست ابنة هو سي.
There's zero resemblance.
لا يوجد أي تشابه.
But there's something oddly familiar about her.
ولكن هناك شيء غريب مألوف عنها.
Who could she look like?
من يمكن أن تبدو مثله؟
What is it?
ما هذا؟
Why are you staring at me like that?
لماذا تحدق بي هكذا؟
No. It's nothing.
لا، لا شيء.
I was just surprised you came to meet me without putting up a fight.
لقد فوجئت للتو بأنك أتيت لمقابلتي دون أي قتال.
I just needed some fresh air. It's a little tense at home.
كنتُ بحاجةٍ إلى بعض الهواء النقي. الجوّ متوترٌ بعض الشيء في المنزل.
Is something going on at home?
هل يحدث شيء في المنزل؟
That's none of your business.
هذا ليس من شأنك.
- Did you meet with her? - I did.
- هل التقيت بها؟ - نعم.
I looked her over with a hawk's eye for a good hour.
لقد نظرت إليها بعين الصقر لمدة ساعة كاملة.
- And? - She's nothing like Min Kyung Chae.
- و؟ - إنها لا تشبه مين كيونغ تشاي على الإطلاق.
- So she must take after her dad. - I don't know about that,
- إذن يجب أن تكون مثل والدها. - لا أعرف عن ذلك،
but as I was looking at her,
ولكن بينما كنت أنظر إليها،
she reminded me of someone.
لقد ذكّرتني بشخص ما.
Who was it?
من كان؟
Never mind.
لا تهتم.
Who is it?
من هذا؟
You don't look so well.
أنت لا تبدو بحالة جيدة.
I'm just tired.
أنا متعب فقط.
Meetings and conferences all day.
اجتماعات ومؤتمرات طوال اليوم.
You should rest. I'll go warm up your herbal medicine.
يجب عليك الراحة. سأذهب لتسخين دوائك العشبي.
About Kyung Chae...
نبذة عن كيونغ تشاي...
I let her go from the company today.
لقد سمحت لها بالخروج من الشركة اليوم.
So you fired her.
إذن قمت بطردها.
Are you upset about it?
هل أنت منزعج بشأن ذلك؟
Upset? If that's what you decided, then that's that.
منزعج؟ إذا كان هذا ما قررته، فهذا هو الأمر.
She grew up with Mingang Distribution, so this won't be easy for her to accept.
لقد نشأت في شركة Mingang Distribution، لذلك لن يكون من السهل عليها قبول هذا الأمر.
It wasn't an easy decision for me either.
ولم يكن القرار سهلا بالنسبة لي أيضًا.
But if I'd kept her on,
ولكن لو أبقيتها،
I was afraid something irreversible might happen.
كنت خائفة من أن يحدث شيء لا رجعة فيه.
I know what you mean.
انا اعرف ماذا تقصد.
I'm fine with it. As long as you're happy, that's all that matters.
أنا راضية. ما دامت سعيدة، هذا كل ما يهم.
The chairman is tired.
الرئيس متعب.
If it's not urgent, come back later.
إذا لم يكن الأمر عاجلاً، عد لاحقًا.
Even if she is the CEO,
حتى لو كانت هي الرئيسة التنفيذية،
she can't just fire me like this.
لا يمكنها أن تطردني بهذه الطريقة.
Personnel decisions are the CEO's prerogative.
قرارات شؤون الموظفين هي من اختصاص الرئيس التنفيذي.
So what are you then, Father? A figurehead?
فماذا أنت إذن يا أبتي؟ هل أنت مجرد رمز؟
If you're just going to let that woman do whatever she wants.
إذا كنت ستسمح لتلك المرأة أن تفعل ما تريد.
This right here is why you were fired.
هذا هو السبب الذي جعلك تُطرد.
If you were going to do this, why did you call me back from the States?
إذا كنت تنوي القيام بهذا، فلماذا اتصلت بي من الولايات المتحدة؟
You should have just let me stay there with the man I love.
كان يجب عليك أن تسمح لي بالبقاء هناك مع الرجل الذي أحبه.
Believe me, I regret it more than you know.
صدقني، أنا نادم على ذلك أكثر مما تتخيل.
I never knew you could sink this low.
لم أكن أعلم أنك قد تنحدر إلى هذا المستوى.
Dumping your own father in a nursing home, playing tricks on someone with allergies,
ترك والدك في دار رعاية المسنين، أو ممارسة الحيل على شخص يعاني من الحساسية،
getting so jealous when someone succeeds that you try to sabotage a deal,
تشعر بغيرة شديدة عندما ينجح شخص ما لدرجة أنك تحاول تخريب الصفقة،
and to top it all off, you even locked a person in the supply room.
ولزيادة الطين بلة، قمت بإغلاق شخص ما في غرفة الإمدادات.
Was that really so wrong?
هل كان ذلك خطأً حقاً؟
Have you lived your entire life without making a single mistake, Father?
هل عشت حياتك كلها دون أن ترتكب خطأ واحدا يا أبي؟
You've never sinned?
هل لم تخطئ أبدا؟
I was just trying to do well. I can't control the outcome!
كنت أحاول فقط أن أحقق نتائج جيدة. لا أستطيع التحكم بالنتيجة!
Can't we just put it behind us?
ألا يمكننا أن نضع هذا الأمر خلفنا؟
What's the point of keeping score between a father and daughter?
ما الفائدة من حساب النتيجة بين الأب وابنته؟
I'll do better.
سأفعل الأفضل.
If you just give me my job back,
إذا أعطيتني وظيفتي مرة أخرى،
I'll work hard to make Mingang Distribution number one in Korea,
سأعمل بجد لجعل شركة Mingang Distribution رقم واحد في كوريا،
no, the number one distribution company in the world.
لا، شركة التوزيع رقم واحد في العالم.
So please, let's just go back to how things were.
لذا من فضلك، دعونا نعود إلى ما كانت عليه الأمور.
Please, Father?
من فضلك يا أبي؟
Let's go back to how it was...
دعونا نعود إلى ما كان عليه الأمر...
before that woman ever came into our company,
قبل أن تأتي تلك المرأة إلى شركتنا،
and before she ever set foot in our home.
وقبل أن تضع قدمها في منزلنا.
It's far too late for that.
لقد فات الأوان لذلك.
Father.
أب.
What are you doing?
ماذا تفعل؟
I'd rather die than be kicked out of the company.
أفضّل أن أموت على أن أُطرد من الشركة.
- What? - Kill me.
- ماذا؟ - اقتلني.
Taking Mingang from me is a death sentence.
إن أخذ مينغانغ مني هو حكم الإعدام.
You've completely lost your mind.
لقد فقدت عقلك تماما.
It would be an honor to die at your hands.
سيكون شرفًا لي أن أموت على يديك.
Since you're Mingang's great founder, the titan of distribution in Korea.
باعتبارك مؤسس شركة مينجانج العظيم، عملاق التوزيع في كوريا.
Are you really going to act like this?
هل ستتصرفين بهذه الطريقة حقا؟
Why?
لماذا؟
Can't bring yourself to do it?
لا تستطيع أن تجبر نفسك على القيام بذلك؟
I guess not. I'm your daughter, after all.
لا أظن ذلك. أنا ابنتك، بعد كل شيء.
Then you have to let me live.
إذن عليك أن تدعني أعيش.
You can't just take Mingang away from me! It's my whole life!
لا يمكنك أن تأخذ مينغانغ مني هكذا! إنها حياتي كلها!
What are you all doing? Get this thing out of here.
ماذا تفعلون جميعًا؟ أخرجوا هذا الشيء من هنا.
Either give me back the CEO position, or kill me right here, right now.
إما أن تعيدوا لي منصب الرئيس التنفيذي، أو تقتلوني هنا والآن.
- This girl has lost it. - Kyung Chae.
- لقد فقدت هذه الفتاة عقلها. - كيونغ تشاي.
- Ms. Kyung Chae! - I said, kill me already!
- السيدة كيونغ تشاي! - قلت، اقتليني بالفعل!
Kill me!
اقتلني!
Let go!
اتركه!
How can you say something so morbid? Asking your own father to kill you.
كيف تقول شيئًا كهذا؟ تطلب من والدك أن يقتلك.
He's right, Kyung Chae. I know you're angry,
إنه محق يا كيونغ تشاي. أعلم أنك غاضب.
but you shouldn't say things like that to your father.
ولكن لا ينبغي لك أن تقول مثل هذه الأشياء لوالدك.
(Mingang Distribution)
(توزيع)
Min Kyung Chae can't get through a day without her sedatives.
لا تستطيع مين كيونج تشاي قضاء يوم واحد دون مهدئاتها.
She's always crying, screaming, and throwing fits.
إنها دائمًا تبكي وتصرخ وتصاب بنوبات غضب.
Why are you telling me this now?
لماذا تقول لي هذا الآن؟
As a wake-up call.
بمثابة جرس إنذار.
That lifeline you're clinging to is about to snap.
إن شريان الحياة الذي تتمسك به على وشك الانقطاع.
So what? You want me to come crawling to you for help?
ماذا إذن؟ أتريدني أن آتي إليك زاحفًا طلبًا للمساعدة؟
Go on. Try me.
إستمر، جرّبني.
Then I'll decide if you're worth saving.
ثم سأقرر إذا كنت تستحق الإنقاذ.
It's better to swallow your pride a little...
من الأفضل أن تبتلع كبريائك قليلاً...
than be an outcast with no support, passed over for promotions,
من أن تكون منبوذا بلا دعم، ويتم تجاهلك في الترقيات،
and then thrown out.
ومن ثم رميها خارجا.
Wouldn't that be such a tragedy?
ألا يعتبر هذا مأساة؟
Play your cards right.
العب أوراقك بشكل صحيح.
Your entire career is in my hands.
حياتك المهنية بأكملها بين يدي.
You don't want to end up like Min Kyung Chae.
لا تريد أن ينتهي بك الأمر مثل مين كيونغ تشاي.
She took a sedative and just fell asleep.
لقد تناولت مهدئًا ونامت للتو.
I've never seen Kyung Chae like this.
لم أرى كيونغ تشاي هكذا من قبل.
I was so shaken up that I didn't even get to the market.
لقد كنت في حالة صدمة شديدة لدرجة أنني لم أتمكن حتى من الوصول إلى السوق.
We'll just have to make do with what's in the house today.
سوف نضطر إلى الاكتفاء بما هو موجود في المنزل اليوم.
Just put the side dishes back in the fridge after you eat.
فقط قم بوضع الأطباق الجانبية في الثلاجة بعد تناولها.
Nobody remembers my birthday.
لا أحد يتذكر عيد ميلادي.
(The late Baek Mi So)
(المرحوم بايك مي سو)
You shouldn't have.
لا ينبغي لك ذلك.
Oh, please. Today is a special day. It's Mi So's birthday!
يا ليت. اليوم يوم مميز. عيد ميلاد مي سو!
When you were in the States, I took care of it on my own,
عندما كنت في الولايات المتحدة، كنت أهتم بالأمر بنفسي،
but now our whole family is finally together again.
لكن الآن أصبحت عائلتنا بأكملها معًا مرة أخرى أخيرًا.
It's Mi So's favorite. Your Auntie's kimchi fried rice and soup.
إنه طبق مي سو المفضل. أرز مقلي بالكيمتشي وحساء عمتك.
Happy birthday, my dear Mi So. Eat up!
عيد ميلاد سعيد يا عزيزتي مي سو. تناولي الطعام!
Looks like Mi So is...
يبدو أن مي سو هو...
getting the royal treatment from her Aunt Yeon Ah.
تحصل على العلاج الملكي من عمتها يون آه.
Come on. It's a happy day. Don't upset Mi So.
هيا، إنه يوم سعيد. لا تزعجوا مي سو.
Yeon Ah.
يون آه.
I'm the new CEO.
أنا الرئيس التنفيذي الجديد.
What?
ماذا؟
For real?
لريال مدريد؟
You're the CEO of Mingang Distribution?
أنت الرئيس التنفيذي لشركة Mingang Distribution؟
So you're really the CEO of that enemy of a company?
إذن أنت حقًا الرئيس التنفيذي لتلك الشركة العدوة؟
Then you can finally get justice for Mi So.
وبعد ذلك يمكنك أخيرًا الحصول على العدالة لمي سو.
Now that company...
الآن تلك الشركة...
won't be able to just throw its weight around anymore.
لن تكون قادرة على إلقاء وزنها حولها بعد الآن.
As long as I'm the CEO,
طالما أنا الرئيس التنفيذي،
I will never let it trample on the powerless.
لن أسمح له أبدًا بالدوس على الضعفاء.
I'll see you at the office.
سأراك في المكتب.
Are you okay?
هل أنت بخير؟
I have to be.
يجب علي أن أكون.
I have an appointment. I'll be back soon.
لدي موعد، سأعود قريبًا.
Don't you even know what today is?
هل لا تعرف حتى ما هو اليوم؟
What's today?
ما هو اليوم؟
You know what? Nevermind.
هل تعلم ماذا؟ لا بأس.
You know what I'm going through.
أنت تعرف ما أمر به.
I don't have the energy to deal with you right now,
ليس لدي الطاقة للتعامل معك الآن،
so just stay out of trouble.
لذلك فقط ابق بعيدًا عن المتاعب.
She's acting like she owns the place, walking all over everyone at work.
إنها تتصرف وكأنها تملك المكان، وتتصرف مثل الجميع في العمل.
It's the same way at home.
إنه نفس الطريقة في المنزل.
Are you just going to stand by and watch?
هل ستقف فقط وتشاهد؟
You think I'm putting up with this because I want to?
هل تعتقد أنني أتحمل هذا لأنني أريد ذلك؟
Isn't this when you should be doing something, Lawyer Kim?
أليس هذا هو الوقت الذي يجب عليك فيه القيام بشيء ما، المحامي كيم؟
With you gone, I'm not powerful enough on my own.
مع رحيلك، لم أعد قويًا بما يكفي بمفردي.
Even the Board has turned its back on me.
حتى أن المجلس أدار ظهره لي.
Then you might as well go talk to Soo Jung.
إذن قد يكون من الأفضل أن تذهب وتتحدث مع سو جونغ.
She's no fan of Lucia either.
وهي ليست من محبي لوسيا أيضًا.
You think she'll just take our side, even as the director?
هل تعتقد أنها ستقف إلى جانبنا، حتى كمخرجة؟
She'd have to risk getting on the chairman's bad side.
سيتعين عليها المخاطرة بالوقوع في الجانب السيئ من الرئيس.
So you're saying there's no way out of this?
إذن أنت تقول أنه لا يوجد مخرج من هذا؟
Not necessarily.
ليس بالضرورة.
As long as we have the chairman's will, we still have a chance.
ما دامت إرادة الرئيس موجودة، فما زالت لدينا الفرصة.
Because the chairman's will clearly states...
لأن إرادة الرئيس تنص بوضوح على...
that in an emergency, you are named as the acting Chairman.
أنه في حالة الطوارئ، يتم تعيينك رئيسًا بالنيابة.
The way things are now,
بالطريقة التي تسير بها الأمور الآن،
I doubt I'll ever get to be the acting Chairman.
أنا أشك في أنني سأصبح رئيسًا بالنيابة على الإطلاق.
As long as the will isn't changed, you'll have an opportunity.
ما دامت الإرادة لم تتغير، سيكون لديك الفرصة.
Then you can step into the Chairman's role...
ومن ثم يمكنك أن تتولى دور الرئيس...
and set everything right.
وأصلح كل شيء.
Why are all the stocks in the distribution industry...
لماذا كل الأسهم في قطاع التوزيع...
tanking like this?
الدبابة مثل هذا؟
Mingang is holding up, but something about it seems fishy.
مينغانغ صامد، لكن هناك شيء مريب فيه.
Does staring at those darn stocks all day put food on the table?
هل النظر إلى تلك الأسهم اللعينة طوال اليوم يوفر الطعام على المائدة؟
What rock have you been living under? It puts food on the table, and then some.
تحت أي صخرة تعيش؟ إنها توفر لك الطعام، بل وأكثر.
It can even get us a car.
ويمكن حتى أن نحصل على سيارة.
Have you ever heard of a stock market tycoon?
هل سبق لك أن سمعت عن قطب سوق الأوراق المالية؟
No, I'm saying the CEO was replaced,
لا، أنا أقول أن الرئيس التنفيذي تم استبداله،
so Mingang will manage to get by somehow.
لذلك سوف يتمكن مينغانغ من النجاح بطريقة أو بأخرى.
But we're the ones in serious trouble.
لكننا نحن الذين نواجه مشكلة خطيرة.
Now that Lucia's the CEO,
الآن بعد أن أصبحت لوسيا هي الرئيس التنفيذي،
our Ja Kyung's in-law troubles are going to get even worse.
ستزداد مشاكل حماتنا جا كيونج سوءًا.
You've got a point. I wonder how Ji Seop is doing with her.
كلامك صحيح. أتساءل كيف حال جي سوب معها.
I think I'll go pay him a visit and see for myself.
أعتقد أنني سأذهب لزيارته وأرى بنفسي.
Blood is thicker than water. Why worry about him before your daughter?
الدم أثقل من الماء. لماذا تقلق عليه قبل ابنتك؟
My lovely wife. You know Ji Seop isn't the brightest bulb.
زوجتي الحبيبة. أنتِ تعلمين أن جي سوب ليس ألمع مصباح.
He's lacking.
إنه ينقصه.
He's a big guy, but he's got nothing between the ears.
إنه رجل كبير الحجم، لكنه لا يملك أي شيء بين أذنيه.
Right.
يمين.
I'm home.
أنا الوطن.
Speak of the devil. Tae Kyung, the man of the hour.
تحدث عن الشيطان. تاي كيونغ، رجل الساعة.
So, how are things at the company?
إذن، كيف تسير الأمور في الشركة؟
The company?
الشركة ؟
The new CEO.
الرئيس التنفيذي الجديد.
He's been here, worried about that all day.
لقد كان هنا، قلقًا بشأن هذا الأمر طوال اليوم.
Our new CEO is doing great.
مديرنا التنفيذي الجديد يقوم بعمل عظيم.
She just landed a deal with the Doil Department Store...
لقد حصلت للتو على صفقة مع متجر Doil Department Store ...
to have our products on their shelves.
أن نضع منتجاتنا على رفوفهم.
Doil Department Store? One of the top three department stores?
متجر دويل؟ أحد أفضل ثلاثة متاجر متعددة الأقسام؟
Does that mean Mingang's stock is going to skyrocket?
هل يعني هذا أن أسهم مينغانغ سترتفع بشكل كبير؟
It's not official yet,
لم يصبح الأمر رسميا بعد
but the price should go up soon.
ولكن السعر من المفترض أن يرتفع قريبًا.
See? I told you! It buys us new cars.
أرأيت؟ لقد أخبرتك! إنه يشتري لنا سيارات جديدة.
If I make a killing this time,
إذا حققت نجاحًا كبيرًا هذه المرة،
I'm going to buy that luxury supercar.
سأشتري تلك السيارة الفاخرة الخارقة.
You're just getting home?
هل وصلت للتو إلى المنزل؟
Are you mad at me or something?
هل أنت غاضب مني أو شيء من هذا القبيل؟
Did I do something wrong?
هل فعلت شيئا خاطئا؟
"Something you did wrong?"
"هل فعلت شيئا خاطئا؟"
As if I could ever forget what you did to my Mi So.
وكأنني أستطيع أن أنسى ما فعلته بمي سو.
No, it's nothing.
لا، لا شيء.
I told you I wasn't the one who sent that text.
لقد قلت لك أنني لست الشخص الذي أرسل هذه الرسالة.
You don't believe me, do you?
أنت لا تصدقني، أليس كذلك؟
I believe you, so just leave.
أنا أصدقك، لذا فقط أرحل.
- I'm tired. - Mom!
- أنا متعب. - أمي!
That word, "Mom."
تلك الكلمة "أمي"
Just for today, can you please not call me that?
لليوم فقط، هل يمكنك من فضلك عدم مناداتي بهذا؟
Why are you being like this?
لماذا أنت هكذا؟
It was my birthday today, but no one remembered.
لقد كان عيد ميلادي اليوم، ولكن لا أحد يتذكره.
I'm not that happy either.
أنا لست سعيدة أيضا.
Today's your birthday?
عيد ميلادك اليوم؟
You had no idea, did you?
لم يكن لديك أي فكرة، أليس كذلك؟
Figures.
أرقام.
Who would remember a birthday for someone like me?
من الذي سيتذكر عيد ميلاد شخص مثلي؟
What's with you?
ماذا بك؟
It's nothing.
لا شئ.
You're not going to tell me what's wrong?
لن تخبرني ما هو الخطأ؟
You didn't know it was my birthday today either, did you?
أنت أيضًا لم تعلم أن اليوم هو عيد ميلادي، أليس كذلك؟
Your birthday?
عيد ميلادك؟
I swear I remembered it just a few days ago.
أقسم أنني تذكرت ذلك منذ أيام قليلة فقط.
What do you want for a present?
ماذا تريد كهدية؟
I wonder if any cake shops are still open.
أتساءل عما إذا كان هناك أي محلات كعكة لا تزال مفتوحة.
I'm not a kid asking for things like that.
أنا لست طفلاً يطلب أشياء كهذه.
It just hurts that everyone in the family forgot.
يؤلمني حقًا أن الجميع في العائلة نسوا الأمر.
And what about Lucia?
وماذا عن لوسيا؟
That stepmother you adore so much didn't bother?
هل لم تهتم زوجة الأب التي تعشقها كثيرًا ؟
See?
يرى؟
I told you you mean nothing to that woman.
لقد قلت لك أنك لا تعني شيئا لتلك المرأة.
No matter what that woman says or does, I told you not to fall for her, didn't I?
بغض النظر عما تقوله أو تفعله تلك المرأة، لقد أخبرتك ألا تقع في حبها، أليس كذلك؟
How can she and Mi So share a birthday?
كيف يمكنها هي ومي سو مشاركة عيد ميلاد واحد؟
What kind of fate connects these two?
ما هو نوع المصير الذي يربط هذين الاثنين؟
I guess no one celebrated her birthday.
أعتقد أن لا أحد احتفل بعيد ميلادها.
Listen carefully.
استمع بعناية.
Just because I got fired doesn't mean this is over.
مجرد أنني تم طردي من وظيفتي لا يعني أن الأمر قد انتهى.
The company will be mine in the end.
ستكون الشركة ملكي في النهاية.
What are you talking about?
ماذا تتحدث عنه؟
If Father can no longer act as chairman, I'm supposed to take his place.
إذا لم يعد والدي قادراً على التصرف كرئيس، فمن المفترض أن أحل محله.
That's what's in the will that Father wrote with his own two hands.
هذا ما هو موجود في الوصية التي كتبها الأب بيديه.
Do you think Father is going to live forever?
هل تعتقد أن الأب سوف يعيش إلى الأبد؟
Once I become the chairman, that woman will lose her position anyway,
بمجرد أن أصبح رئيسًا، فإن تلك المرأة سوف تفقد منصبها على أي حال،
and she'll be kicked out of this house without a penny.
وسوف يتم طردها من هذا المنزل دون فلس واحد.
As long as the will isn't changed,
طالما أن الإرادة لم تتغير،
Mingang, this house, and even you...
مينغانغ، هذا البيت، وحتى أنت...
will all be mine.
كل ذلك سيكون لي.
Acting chairman?
رئيس بالنيابة؟
Min Kyung Chae.
مين كيونغ تشاي.
So that was your ace in the hole all along.
لقد كان هذا هو ورقتك الرابحة طوال الوقت.
(The Woman Who Swallowed the Sun)
(المرأة التي ابتلعت الشمس)
Once she takes over as acting chairman, it's all over.
بمجرد توليها منصب الرئيس بالنيابة، فإن كل شيء سينتهي.
There are only two ways to stop Min Kyung Chae.
هناك طريقتان فقط لإيقاف مين كيونغ تشاي.
She thinks if I'm gone, Mingang is hers?
هل تعتقد أنه إذا رحلت، فإن مينغانغ ستكون لها؟
So that’s what she's thinking.
إذن هذا ما تفكر فيه.
Do you want to see me go down like this?
هل تريد أن تراني أسقط هكذا؟
If I go down, so do you, Kim Sun Jae.
إذا نزلت، فسوف تنزل أنت أيضًا، كيم سون جاي.
There is one way,
هناك طريقة واحدة،
but it'll be my final, all-or-nothing move.
لكنها ستكون خطوتي النهائية، إما كل شيء أو لا شيء.
When is the right time to use this to deal them a fatal blow?
متى يكون الوقت المناسب لاستخدام هذا لتوجيه ضربة قاتلة لهم؟
I think it's time to make some revisions to my will.
أعتقد أنه حان الوقت لإجراء بعض المراجعات على وصيتي.
(Subtitles are provided by KOCOWA.)
(يتم توفير الترجمة بواسطة KOCOWA.)